So AI voice agents can do pretty much
anything. Whether it is attract you more
leads, save time, manage your calendar,
grow your business, or even automate
your work. Plus, it's a massively
growing market. I mean, look at this
trend chart, right? I don't have to
explain that this is a very, very good
time to get into the voice AI agent
game. If you still don't have a voice
agent in your life or business, you're
honestly missing out. So, in this video,
I'll show you how to build a voice AI
agent from scratch, even if you are a
complete beginner. Now, you have to
realize that every single business needs
voice agents. or if you don't have a
business, you could be one of the many
people selling to the 350 million
registered companies worldwide. Now,
another reason to take voice agent
seriously is that this is the next big
modality in the AI game. When JBD came
out in 23, it was all about texting.
Same with 24 and the first half of 2025.
But the future is not texting. The
future is voice speaking. Whether it is
through meta glasses, whether it is
through phone, through headphones,
doesn't matter. Voice is the modality of
the future. And that's because talking
is just way faster than typing. Most
people type at like 40 words per minute,
which is disgusting. For most people,
speaking is like three times faster than
typing. Also, people don't realize just
how hyperrealistic voice agents have
recently gotten. Over 95% of people
cannot even tell if they're speaking to
one of the cutting edge voice models.
But it's not just about the AI voice
itself. You can even simulate ambient
sounds and pauses, which makes it even
more realistic. Plus, voice is just
convenient, right? You can talk to it
whether you're in a car, walking,
whether you're cycling or inside of a
meeting. Plus, voice is going to be much
bigger market than text purely by the
fact that there's billions of people in
this world that aren't really literate
when it comes to writing or texting, but
they can speak, which means voice by
default will be a bigger market. Just
like smartphones are a bigger market
than personal computers. But the best
part is voice agents are actually very
easy to build. By the end of this video,
if you actually pay attention, you will
have your very first AI voice agent
deployed and running in your life or
business. And no, you don't have to be a
programmer to do this. All right, so let
me show you the agent itself. And as I
promised, it's very simple, right? We
have the web hook trigger. We have the
AI agent using OpenAI model. Then we
have the tools. Obviously, you can
customize this for whatever you want.
I'll show you how to do that in a bit.
And then we have a respond to web hook,
which is literally the simplest note
ever. First incoming item. This is what
the agent returns. So yes, building
voice agents is very simple. And yes,
you can do it. Just pay attention. Give
me 20 minutes and you will have your
first voice agent in your life. Now, the
voice agent looks something like this.
So, let me show you how this voice agent
can sound.
>> Thanks for calling Sharlook Barberhop,
mister. Are you looking to book, change,
or cancel an appointment or ask a quick
question?
>> Now, believe it or not, businesses are
throwing money at voice agents like
this. I mean, in just a few minutes, I
was able to find multiple four-f
figureure listings on Upwork where
people want AI, voice system automation,
voice AI agent, voice agent, voice
receptionist. Now, the biggest problems
that beginners make is they build AI
agents that do not run 24/7. An AI agent
is only useful when it can be available
at all times, right? If you have a
business and you want to call your AI
voice secretary, she's not available,
useless. One of the ways to solve this
is with any 10 cloud, but the problem is
it can get expensive. Plus, there's a
limit on the amount of executions. But
luckily, there's a very simple solution,
and that is HostingerVPS. Not only is
this super cheap, but it's also what I
personally use for all of the AI agents
in my company because it is just so easy
to set up. Let me show you. If you get
the KVM2 plan, which I would recommend
you to get, you can literally run
hundreds of AI agents on this plan, and
it will cost you way less than if you
used the NA10 Cloud, especially if you
go with the 24-month option, which I
definitely recommend you do because you
want your AI agents running forever. You
build them once and they save you time
in perpetuity. And since Hosting Group
was kind enough to sponsor this video,
if you use the coupon code David, you
will save additional 10% off on your
annual or two-year plan. Then what
remains is selecting the server
location. So just select whatever is
closest to you and then for the
operating system, click on NA10. They
literally have a one-click install
template for NA10. It couldn't be any
easier. So click on confirm and then
click on continue and login with your
Hostinger account or just create one.
And the last thing that remains is
filling out your billing details and
your credit card. I've been using
Hostinger for months to host my entered
agents and it really is the simplest and
most affordable way to do so. So again,
make sure to check out the link
description and remember to use code
David to get 10% off. All right, so once
you have your Hostinger VPS, go to the
panel, click on home and select manage.
Here we can see how our virtual private
server is running and all the usage you
see about it. So this is another
advantage over the N10 cloud. You can
actually see this data that N10
otherwise wouldn't give you. So all we
need to click is manage app and this
will launch the NA10 server where we can
see all of our AI agents. Okay. So now
let me show you how to build this agent
inside of NA10 from scratch. So the
first thing we have to do is choose the
trigger. We're going to use the web hook
one. So type in web hook. There we go.
Now if this is your first time in NA10,
you might be thinking, "Okay, David,
this feels complicated. I don't know
what to do." Calm down. The data on the
left is what's coming in. In the middle,
this is this node. This is how we
process data. And on the right, this is
the output, right? This is how every
single node inside of N10 looks. Once
you realize that, you realize, okay,
it's actually not that hard. So, we need
to change just a few things inside of
this web hook note. First of all, we
will need the production URL. This is
what we will add later to our voice
agent. But the main thing is changing
the HTTP method to post. And the second
thing you have to change is respond to
using respond node web hook. This is
going to be after the AI agent runs. And
that should be it. So, make sure to save
in the top right inside of any 10. After
making any changes, always click save.
That way, you don't lose your progress.
Now after the web hook, we need to feed
the data into an AI agent. So type in AI
agent. Boom. Now this is the main part
of our operation, right? This is the
agent that decides what tools are being
used, which model is being used, how we
output the web hook. Anything you want
to build, you can do it with this agent.
So for the prompt, let's click on define
below. And for the user message, we're
just going to pass the transcription
from the call. So that's going to be
included in the web hook. Next up, we
need to scroll all the way at the bottom
and click on add option and add a system
prompt, right? because we want to have
control over how our AI agent behaves
and the way we do that is with the
system message. Now, if you click on
expression, you can actually click this
expand button to have a bit more space
for this. And I already prepared a
system prompt, so feel free to pause and
copy it. But basically, this demo is
going to be for a booking agent, right?
So, this could be used for a barber
shop. This could be used for dental
agency. I mean, any brickandmortar
business can use this agent. So, you can
literally take it and resell it to
actual companies. Now, one detail is the
time zone, right? If you have all
customers in the same time zone, such as
a small country like Czech Republic,
then it's fine doing it like so, where
you define the time zone for everybody.
But if your customers are worldwide,
then make sure to tell the agent, please
ask the user which time zone he's
calling from, right? So that anything
with time such as booking or
appointments, whatever will be accurate
in the user's time zone. But other than
that, this prompt is actually very
simple. So once you set up the agent,
again, make sure to save and we need to
give it a model. That's the brain of the
AI agent. without a model it cannot
think. You can use OpenAI, you can use
Enthropic, Google, whatever you prefer.
I'm just going to use OpenAI because
GPD4.1 is perhaps the most reliable
model for AI agents right now. Now, if
this is your first time setting up an
OpenAI model, you obviously have to pass
your API key, which you can do in this
credential right here. To get your API
key, just go to platform.openi.com,
log in with your Chip account on the
left, click on API keys, and then click
on create new secret key. Very simple,
takes 30 seconds. Okay, so back to NA10,
we added the model. So now our AI agent
has a chat model. So let's save that
again. By the way, later in the video,
I'll show you how to actually profit
with voice AI agents, whether it is
integrating them into your own business
or selling it to other companies. So
stay tuned for that. The next thing we
need to add is a tool. So in this
example, let's do Google calendar.
That's something that anyone uses and
anybody can implement right now. The
first step is selecting which account it
should be connected with. I've shown
that in dozens of other videos, so just
watch any of these. It's not that
complicated. Now, the important thing is
the operation here. We need to change
this to get many. Before it can make any
changes to the calendar, you need to
check where the empty slots are. So,
again, select the calendar you want it
to use. And here's the fun part. For all
of these, we can just click on let the
model define. All of these will let the
AI agent decide how to use these and how
to fill these in. We don't have to fill
these. Like, this is the beauty of
building AI agents in 2025. It's way
easier, way simpler than people think.
So also make sure to rename it to get
many. That way it's organized and we
know what each tool does. Now we need a
second tool again, Google calendar. And
by the way, you can add way more tools
than that. Each agent can have 10 plus
tools until it starts getting confused.
And then if it starts getting confused,
guess what? We can add another AI agent
as a sub agent. This is something that's
new to NA10. So even if you need to add
like 20 plus tools where in the past
that would be too much for a single
agent, right? it would get confused, not
sure which to call, when to call each
tool. Now you can do sub agent that
would be like managing all calendar
tools for example, right? Or like one
agent that manages all email tools and
that agent has like five email tools and
it's hyper specialized to just email
operations. So that we can do with sub
agents but in this example we don't even
need to do that and I don't want to make
it harder on you. All we need to do is
just use two two different tools get
many and then create event. So let's
rename that calendar create event.
Again, choose the account to connect
with. Under operation, make sure to
leave it on create and select the target
calendar. Now, just like before, we
don't want to define these. We just want
to let the model decide. So let's click
on this and AI will decide these for us.
And the same goes for the description
and the summary. So again, click on this
button. Boom. Boom. And the AI agent
will fill these up without you having to
tell it anything. Now, as you can see,
our AI agent is starting to take shape.
I told you building a agents is easier
and faster than you think. If you can
sit down for 60 minutes and commit to
it, you will automate a single process
for the rest of your life and save time
whereas everyone else who doesn't do it
has a disadvantage. So building a few
voice agents is one of the easiest way
to get an unfair advantage over 99% of
people. Now to finish this up, we need
to finish the web hook, right? So type
in web hook, respond to web hook. There
we go. And just leave it on first
incoming item. And that's literally it.
Just like that, our AI agent inside of
NA10 is complete. Okay, so now that our
NA10 agent is done, we need to integrate
the voice agent with it, which actually
is even simpler. Real quick, if you are
serious about AI, you have to start
using Vector. Here is what our users
say. I just installed Vector today after
watching many of David's videos and holy
crap, this tool is insane. Just tell it
what to do and it does it. Move tasks
around, simplifies things. It's really
like having a personal assistant. And I
haven't even gotten to trying out the
agents yet. And by the way, this is just
one of the 60,000 plus people that are
currently using Vectal. And since you
love NA10, let me give you exclusive
sneak peek of a feature that we're
releasing today called workflows. So
inside of Veectal, on the right, you'll
see a new button right here where you
can access your workflows. Now, what are
workflows? They're basically many
automations inside of your Rectal. So,
for example, you can have it run every 3
hours to create an idea. And the action
could be create idea, how to get closer
towards reaching my goals. Boom. Save
the workflow and then in your idea inbox
you can see every 5 minutes a new idea
will appear how to get closer towards
reaching your goals. And this is just
one of many workflows you can create
inside of vectal. Since you're already
watching a video about building AI
agents, I know you are a serious
individual that wants to be as
productive as possible. And trust me,
you will love Vectal. This is an AI
first productivity app that does your
tasks for you. And the best part is you
can try it completely for free. Just go
to vectal.ai and sign up. All right. So
for the voice agent, I decided to use
retail. You can also use Vappy or any
other alternative, but retail makes it
super simple. So just click on try for
free. And this is what we'll connect to
our calendar agent right here to do the
realistic human voice. So inside of
retail, you can start without adding
your payment. There's $10 for free. So
on the top right, click on create agent,
voice agent. Click on single prompt
agent and start from blank. Create. The
first thing we need to do is choose the
model. So you can use GBT5 if you want
maximum performance. If you want a bit
faster, GBD5 mini is also great. So you
can do the fast here. Boom. Then we need
to set a system prompt. So I prepared a
demo prompt for a barber. Again, feel
free to pause and take it and modify it.
But feel free to modify this for your
own business. Right? This is going to be
just a random stuff for a barber shop.
So unless you're running a barber shop,
it's probably not going to be directly
relevant to you. But you can have a
voice agent managing your calendar,
doing your emails, whatever you want it
to do. So then click on save. Scroll
down below the prompt and make sure to
select AI speaks first. Then select
custom message. This will ensure that
the AI agent always starts the
conversation and doesn't wait for the
human input. Next up, let's go to speech
settings right here and let's select the
background noise. This is very important
to making it sound super realistic. You
can choose any of these. Uh I think
coffee shop is the best one. But the
most important is this functions right
here. This is where we can connect our
voice agent to our NAT agent right here.
So click on add. Click on custom
function. Name it calendar agent. Give
it a clear description such as this tool
is to check the available times on the
users's calendar. After giving the
available times, this tool will be used
again to book the available time slot.
Now, as far as the endpoint, this is
where we need to go back into any click
on the original web hook trigger. Click
on production URL. Copy this. Just click
on that. Go back to retail and paste it
in here. And then scroll all the way
down and enable speak during execution
and disable speak after execution. And
just like that, we've connected our two
AI agents. It wasn't hard at all. Now,
before we test it out, let me also show
you how to select the different voices,
right? So, here we can select between 11
labs, OpenAI, Cartisia. You can go
through these. There's like dozens. Um,
if you want like a middle-aged, old,
young, male, female, English, Australian
accent, Indian accent, whatever you
want, they have it all here. But more
important than the voice is the
finetuning of the model. So, this is the
voice model that's powering it. So by
auto it's 11 laps turbo V2. This is very
decent. You can also use the V2.5 if you
want even faster. The flash is the
fastest one. But uh then you want to
customize the voice speed. I recommend
going like 1.1 otherwise it's too fast.
Default is also fine. Voice temperature.
This is how emotional or column it
should be. I think for businesses a bit
on the colmer side works well. And the
volume you can do a bit louder. These
settings I would recommend for most
voice agents. So click on save. All
right. All right, let me show you a
quick demo of the voice agent. First of
all, we have to enable the automation
inside of NA then. So, enable it that
way it's active right here at the top.
Switch back to retail and we're going to
start the test audio right here. By the
way, let me show you. Calendar has
nothing at 3 p.m. So, actually, first
I'm going to ask about 2 p.m. to see if
it finds this event and if it declines
and then it's going to suggest
alternatives. Let's see. This is
powerful. It can do a lot. Let me show
you.
>> Hello. How can I help you today?
Uh, I need to book a haircut for
tomorrow at 2 p.m. Are you available?
>> Let me check availability for tomorrow
at 2 p.m. for a haircut. Mister, 2 p.m.
tomorrow isn't free. Here are the next
openings. 3:00, 3:45 p.m., 4:45, 5:30
p.m., 8:45, 9:30 p.m. Which time would
you like?
>> Okay, I guess let's do the 3 p.m.
>> Booking the haircut tomorrow at 3 p.m.
for 45 minutes.
>> Boom. There we go. and it booked the
haircut. So even if I it checked my
calendar, it see okay, I have vector
call at 2 p.m. and it rejected it and it
successfully booked it at 3 p.m. So we
can see the executions here in NA10.
First it ran the get many right the get
many tool to see our calendar to check
what are the three slots and then it do
use the create tool create event to add
the tool into my calendar at the correct
time and you can use this for yourself
for your internal team automation and
you know internal usage or you can
actually profit with this by selling it
to companies because every single
company in the next five years will want
to add this especially brick and mortar
companies. So you might be thinking,
okay, David, but how do I actually make
money with this? Well, you should
specialize in one niche and ideally a
niche that you understand. Could be
consulting, could be coffee shops,
mechanics, barbers, whatever you have
some experience or some passion or you
can resonate to them, target that niche.
Plus, if you specialize on one niche,
you can build pre-built agents for that
niche. So, you can literally build it,
have it 80% done, and then just sell it
to that niche, customize the last 20% so
it's relevant to them, right? Like we
here we have some like fake name,
sharplook, barber shop, stuff like that.
But if you target one niche, you save
yourself so much time. You can customize
your marketing, customize your
targeting, customize your messaging,
your offer to that niche. And since the
perceived value of voice agents is much
higher than just a chatbot icon in the,
you know, bottom of website. Let's be
honest, everybody hates those AI chatbot
icons. Everybody wants to talk to a
human. And the reason is because people
execute them terribly, right? They don't
know what you're doing. They are not
watching this channel. They're not
locked in. They're not paying attention.
They don't know what the latest and
greatest models are. So, people hate
these chat bots. But a voice agent has a
much higher perceived value. And if
you're really locked in, you can even
build an agent that will create the
custom prompts for each new business
that you're onboarding. So, you can
automate most of the custom work as
well. And as I showed you earlier, just
with a few minutes of browsing Upwork,
there is hundreds of different companies
looking. And you can see posted two days
ago, posted three days ago, 5 days ago,
people are willing to pay thousands of
dollars for voice agents. So, if you're
still not building voice agents in 2025,
please use this as the proof you need to
get started. I've showed you everything.
I've showed you how to build it in NA10,
how to connect it to retail, and how to
set it up on Hostinger. You watch the
video, you know what to do. Now, it's
time to take action. And Hostinger makes
the deploying super easy and super
affordable as well. Again, thank you
Hostinger for sponsoring this video.
Make sure to use my link below. Use the
code David to save additional 10% off.
And with that being said, thank you guys
for watching and have a wonderful,
productive week.